Feel the Wrath.
Wrath of the Titans is a fantasy, adventure, action
film directed by Jonathan Liebesman.
Perseus tries to live a quieter life as a village fisherman while – dangerously weakened by humanity's lack of
devotion – the gods are losing control of the long-imprisoned Titans and their ferocious leader, Kronos.
Perseus, played by Sam Worthington.
Zeus, played by Liam Neeson.
Hades, played by Ralph Fiennes.
Andromeda, played by Rosamund Pike.
Hephaestus, played by Bill Nighy.
Ares, played by Edgar Ramírez.
Wrath of the Titans is a 2012 action fantasy film and a
sequel to the 2010 film Clash of the Titans.
The film stars Sam Worthington, Rosamund Pike, Bill Nighy, Édgar Ramírez, Toby Kebbell, Danny Huston, Ralph Fiennes, and Liam Neeson, with
Jonathan Liebesman directing a screenplay by Dan Mazeau and David Leslie Johnson from a story by them and Greg Berlanti.
Wrath of the Titans takes place a decade after the events of the preceding film as the gods lose control over the imprisoned Titans (thanks to humanity's lack of
prayers which also is draining their immortality) and Perseus is called, this time to rescue his father Zeus, overthrow the Titans, and save mankind.
Talk of a sequel began with the release of Clash of the Titans in March 2010.
Writers Dan Mazeau and David Leslie Johnson were hired in June 2010 and
director Jonathan Liebesman was brought on board in August 2010.
The majority of the casting took place between January and February 2011.
Principal photography began in London in March 2011.
Like its predecessor, the film was converted to 3D in post-production.
Wrath of the Titans was released in 2D and 3D on
March 30, 2012, in the United States.
The film received mostly negative reviews from critics and grossed
$302 million worldwide on a budget of $150 million.
A sequel entitled Revenge of the Titans was planned for a 2013 release, but was
cancelled due to Wrath's underperformance and too few ideas for a script.
The film explores themes of hades, mythology, greek mythology, zeus, god.